New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides; Records apap151
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneous Files, 1908-2000; 5; 33.25 cubic ft.
  - Subseries 6: School / IPM, Undated; 5.6
    - Northwest Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides, 1990 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 25)
    - NRDC: Children and Pesticides, 1997 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 26)
    - NY Times, "Parents Pressuring Schools for Alternatives to Pesticides", 1994-1995 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 27)
    - NYCAP Action Kit, 1997 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 28)
    - NYCAP Fact Sheet and Reports Sheet, Undated (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 29)
    - NYCAP IPM Guides and Information Clearinghouse Brochure, Undated (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 30)
    - NYCAP -- IPM Information Packet, 1986-1995 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 31)
    - NYCAP News, 1994 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 32)
    - NYCAP Packets on Schools, 1988; 1990; Undated (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 33)
    - NYCAP, "Pesticides and Pest Management in Schools, Institutions, and Other Workplaces: A Resource Guide", 1990 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 34)
    - NYCAP Resource / Information / Outreach, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 35)
    - NYCAP School Campaign, 1990-1994 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 36)
    - NYCAP, School Pesticide Fact Sheet and Safe School Challenge [Sample Press Release], Undated (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 37)
    - NYCAP, Schools and Outreach, 1999; Undated (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 38)
    - NYPIRG NYC Safe Schools handbook, Undated (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 39)
    - NYS Association for Superintendents of School Buildings and Ground / NYCAP -- Survey on IPM, 1997 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 40)
    - Organic School Lunches, 1993 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 41)
    - Oswego School Participant Roster, 1998 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 42)
    - Oswego Schools, 1996 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 43)
    - Overview of Pest Management Policies, Programs and Practices in Selected California Public School Districts, 1996 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 44)
    - Partnership for Children's Health and the Environment / Healthy Schools Network, 2000 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 45)
    - Partnerships for Health Schools -- Information Requests, Financial and Miscellaneous, 1995-1998 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 46)
    - Partnerships for Healthy Schools / w. Alton Jones Foundation -- Reports, 1996-1998 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 47)
    - Partnerships for Healthy Schools [PHS] Partners, 1996-1998 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 48)
    - Partnership for Pesticide-Free-Schools: General Interest Meeting, 1999 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 49)
    - Partnerships for Pesticide-Free-Schools / IPM, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 50)
    - Pennsylvania Schools IPM, 1992 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 51)
    - Pest Management Policies -- Massachusetts, 1999-2001 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 52)
    - Pesticide Exposure Incidents, 2000 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 53)
    - Pesticide Neighbor Notification Law and Schools, New York State, 2001-2002 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 54)
    - Pesticide Neighbor Notification [PNN] / Schools Press Release, 2002; Undated (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 55)
    - Pesticide Notification-School Survey, 2001 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 56)
    - Pesticide Use in Schools -- Miscellaneous, 1993-2002 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 57)
    - Pesticide Watch Education Fund, Reducing Pesticide Use in Schools: An Organizing Manual, 1998 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 58)
    - Pesticides in Schools and Workplaces Resource Guides, Undated (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 59)
    - Pesticides, Neighbor Notification and Schools, 2001-2002 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 60)
    - PHS Database, Undated (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 61)
    - PHS Outreach, Undated (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 62)
    - PHS Proposal for 1998, Undated (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 63)
    - PHS Resources, 1996-1997 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 64)
    - PHS Survey, 1996-1997 (Box 5 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 65)
    - Resources for Integrated Pest Management, NYCAP, 1986-1996 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 1)
    - Revised School Packet on IPM, 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 2)
    - Right-to-Know: Maryland School Notification, 1997 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 3)
    - Riley, Becky, "Getting Pesticides out of Our Schools", 1994 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 4)
    - Rochester Schools Workshop, 1999 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 5)
    - Safe Control of Head Lice, NYCAP, 1997-1998 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 6)
    - San Diego School IPM, 1991 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 7)
    - Schenectady Schools, 1987; 1990-1991 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 8)
    - School Board, 1989-1993 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 9)
    - School Building and Grounds IPM, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 10)
    - School Curricula for Least-Toxic Pest Control / IPM, 1983-1998; Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 11)
    - School District Facilities Department Manual, Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 12)
    - The School Environment: A Strategy Session, 1990 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 13)
    - School Environmental Protection Act of 2001 [SEPA], 1999-2001 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 14)
    - School Environmental Quality, 1988-1994; Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 15)
    - School Indoor Air Quality, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 16)
    - School Indoor Air Quality Best Management Practices Manual, 1995 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 17)
    - School IPM Activist Packet, NYCAP, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 18)
    - School IPM-Ants and Stinging Insects, 1998; Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 19)
    - School IPM Checklist, NYCAP, ca. 1990 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 20)
    - School IPM: Children's Projects, 1983-1998 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 21)
    - School IPM, Collection of Information by NYCAP, 1997-2000 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 22)
    - School IPM Conference [Westchester]- Evaluations, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 23)
    - School IPM-Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 24)
    - School IPM Fact sheets, 2001; Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 25)
    - School IPM: How To, 1990-1997 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 26)
    - School IPM: NCAP, 1989-1994; Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 27)
    - School/IPM -- NYCAP Action Kit Material, 1994-1999 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 28)
    - School IPM Policies -- Various, 1989-1999; Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 29)
    - School IPM Raffle and Winners, 1997 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 30)
    - School IPM Resources -- Rutgers, Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 31)
    - School IPM: Risks of Pesticides, 1991-1997 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 32)
    - Pesticides in Schools, NCAMP / Safer Pest Control Project, 1992-2000 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 33)
    - Pesticides in Schools News clippings, 1988; 1990; 1998; 2000 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 34)
    - Pesticide Watch -- Schools, 1997 (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 35)
    - Pesticides in Schools, General Information, 1990-1995; Undated (Box 6 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 36)
    - School Packet, 1990-1991 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 1)
    - School Packet, 1991-1992 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 2)
    - School Pest Control Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 3)
    - School Pesticide News Clippings, 1985; 1988; 1990-1995 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 4)
    - School Pesticide Use -- State Laws, 2000-2002; Undated (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 5)
    - School TIPS -- Pesticides and IPM -- NYCAP, Undated (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 6)
    - The Schooling of State Pesticide Laws, Beyond Pesticides / NYCAMP, 1998-2000 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 7)
    - Schools -- Cost Savings through IPM, 1997-1998 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 8)
    - Sick School Syndrome, 1993-1995; Undated (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 9)
    - Solomon Schechter School IPM, 2000 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 10)
    - Southeast Schools IPM, 1990-1991 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 11)
    - Successful School IPM Programs, 1999 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 12)
    - SUNY Albany Pesticide Report, 2000 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 13)
    - SUNY Oneonta Pesticide Use, 2002 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 14)
    - Survey, School IPM, 1997 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 15-16)
    - Survey -- School Pesticide Use Reduction, 1995 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 17)
    - Susquehanna Valley Incident, 1993 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 18)
    - Teaching Students About Pesticides, 1989; 1992 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 19)
    - Tennessee Schools IPM, 1993-1994 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 20)
    - Texas Pesticide Information Network, Pesticide Report Card: Texas Schools Score from A to F in the IPM Program, 1999 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 21)
    - Texas Schools IPM, 1994; Undated (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 22)
    - Ticonderoga School Participant Roster, 2000 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 23)
    - Troy -- IPM Policy, 2000 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 24)
    - Tvedten, Stephen L. The Best Control. ..[An Intelligent Pest Management Manual], Ch. 1-13, 1994-1995 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 25)
    - Tvedten, Stephen L. The Best Control. ..[An Intelligent Pest Management Manual], Ch. 14-33, 1994-1995 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 26)
    - Tvedten, Stephen L. The Best Control. ..[An Intelligent Pest Management Manual], Ch. 34-End, 1994-1995 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 27)
    - University at Buffalo Pesticide Report, 2000 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 28)
    - University of Rochester Environmental Health and Safety Dept., IPM Presentation, 1998 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 29)
    - Urban Pest Management for Elementary Students, 1983 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 30)
    - U.S. EPA, Help! It's a Roach! A Roach Prevention Activity Book for Kids, 1999 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 31)
    - U.S. EPA, Pest Control in the School Environment: Adopting Integrated Pest Management, 1993 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 32)
    - U.S. General Accounting Office, Pesticides: Use, Effects and Alternatives to Pesticides in Schools, 1999 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 33)
    - U.S. General Services Administration, GSA Custodial Management Handbook -- Ch. 8: IPM, ca. 1990 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 34)
    - Various School IPM Policies, 1997-1999 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 35)
    - W. Alton Jones Foundation Annual Reports, 1993; 1995 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 36)
    - W. Alton Jones Foundation Application Material, 1995 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 37)
    - W. Alton Jones Foundation Grant Extension and Agreement, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 38)
    - W. Alton Jones Foundation PHS Report, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 39)
    - W. Alton Jones Foundation PHS Report, 1996 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 40)
    - W. Alton Jones Foundation Proposal, 1995 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 41)
    - W. Alton Jones Foundation Proposal for 1997, 1996 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 42)
    - Washington State Schools IPM, 1999 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 43)
    - Webster Central School IPM, 1990-1991 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 44)
    - Westchester Planning / Pesticide Education Project, 2002 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 45)
    - Westchester Schools Participant Roster, 1998 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 46)
    - Westport Central School -- IPM Case Study, 1993-2001 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 47)
    - What is IPM?, 1999; Undated (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 48)
    - Who's Minding the Schools, Fordham Environmental Law Journal, Vol. 7, 1996 Fall (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 49)
    - Wilkenfield, Irene Articles and Biography, 1993 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 50)
    - WWF Canada, 1998 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 51)
    - Playgrounds-Pesticide Use at Schools, 1983; 1987 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 52)
    - Power Lines and Health Risks at Schools, 1993 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 53)
    - PTA -- National, 1990-1993 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 54)
    - PTA -- New York State, 1993; 1997 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 55)
    - Public Citizen -- School Pesticides, 1991-1992 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 56)
    - Quick Guide to Who, What, Where, Why, When and How of IPM for Schools, NYCAP, 1996 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 57)
    - Radon in Schools, 1993; Undated (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 58)
    - Reducing Pesticide Use in Schools, by Phil Boise and Karen Feeney, 1998 (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 59)
    - Reports of "Our Children at Risks", Undated (Box 7 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 60)
  - Subseries 7: Subject Files, Undated; 5.7
    - Access to Pesticide Information, Notes, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 1)
    - Adirondack Park / Adirondack Council, Publications and Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 2)
    - Albany Pine Bush Preserve, 1996-2000 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 3)
    - "The Americans with Disabilities Act as a Weapon Against Indoor Pollution", by Alice Kaswan, 1993 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 4)
    - Anti-Microbial Pesticides, 2001 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 5)
    - Apartments and Condominiums -- Combating Pesticide Use, 1988-1996 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 6)
    - Art Supplies -- Hazards, 2000-2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 7)
    - Asking About Pesticide Use, 1994; Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 8)
    - ATSDR Fact Sheets, 1995-2001 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 9)
    - Bibliography for Research and Writing, NRDC/NYCAP, 1997 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 10)
    - Biodiversity, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 11)
    - Biofungicide, 2000-2001 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 12)
    - Bioherbicide, 2001 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 13)
    - Biological Pesticides, 1991-2000 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 14)
    - Botanical Insecticides, 1985-1998 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 15)
    - "Bromide Barons", 1997 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 16)
    - Building Leadership Teams for Research Protection, 1993 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 17)
    - Buildings -- Healthy/Green, 2001-2002; Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 18)
    - Canadian Pesticide Issues, Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 19)
    - Cancelled Pesticides -- Federal, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 20)
    - CCA [Chromated Copper Arsenate] -- Arsenic Planning, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 21)
    - CCA [Chromated Copper Arsenate] -- Arsenic, Sandra Steingraber, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 22)
    - CCA [Chromated Copper Arsenate] -- Correspondence, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 23)
    - CCA [Chromated Copper Arsenate] -- Deborah Bame, "The Problem with Pressure Treated Wood", Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 24)
    - CCA [Chromated Cooper Arsenate] -- General Information, 2001-2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 25)
    - CCA -- New York State Assembly Bill to ban use of arsenic treated wood, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 26)
    - CCA [Chromated Cooper Arsenate] -- "The Poisonwood Rivals" A report on the dangers of touching arsenic treated wood", 2001 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 27)
    - CCA [Chromated Cooper Arsenate] -- Public Interest Groups petition, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 28)
    - CCA [Chromated Cooper Arsenate] -- Press Correspondence, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 29)
    - CCA [Chromated Cooper Arsenate] -- Studies on testing arsenic levels, 1993-2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 30)
    - CCA Study [Chromated Cooper Arsenate] -- Allison Lounsbury, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 31)
    - CCA Study [Chromated Cooper Arsenate] -- Arsenic in Playgrounds Notes, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 32)
    - CCA Study -- "Chemical Leaching of As, Cu and Cr from CCA Pressure Treated Wood in Children's Playgrounds", 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 33)
    - CCA Study -- "Chemical Leaching of CCA Pressure Treated Wood in Children's Playgrounds", Master Copy, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 34)
    - CCA Study [Chromated Cooper Arsenate] Drafts of Study Press Release, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 35)
    - CCA Study[Chromated Cooper Arsenate] -- "Poison Playgrounds" Press Release, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 36)
    - CCA Study [Chromated Cooper Arsenate] -- Press Conference, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 37)
    - CCA Study [Chromated Cooper Arsenate] -- Project 2002, Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 38)
    - Chemical Fact sheets -- New York State Department of Health, 1989 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 39)
    - Chemical Free Insecticides, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 40)
    - Chemical Injury Information Network, Introductory Package into the World of Toxic Chemicals, ca. 1998 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 41)